Poonam Jangid (1) Featured

Sr. Project Assistance seeking roles as machine learning (AI/ML) engineer in Software Development, Application Programming, Project Management, Algorithm Development, Software Design, Web Development, Data Science, Machine Learning, Python, MATLAB, Embedded C



Current Designation: none Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: none Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period

Current Location: Ahmedabad Highest Degree: M.Tech [Instrumentation]

Pref. Location: Delhi / NCR, Ahmedabad, Bengaluru / Bangalore Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: sr. project assistance, software developer, software development, application programming, project

management, algorithm development, software design, web development, data science, machine

learning,python,matlab,embedded c,c++,NLP,Computer Vision

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

Experienced Fellow with a demonstrated history of working in the research industry. Skilled in Control System, Matlab, Programming, Machine Learning/Deep Learning with experience in real time implementation of Computer Vision and Al algorithms on Embedded system. Strong research professional with a Master's Degree focused in Applied Instrumentation and multidisciplinary experience.

Work Experience

none as none Feb 2018 to Till Date

Csir Ceeri as senior project assistant

Feb 2018 to Mar 2020

Responsibilities are to assist in designing and development of Embedded Control System for providing excitation signal and measurement system o Develop the Al based Closed loop and Feed Forward Control algorithms for highly nonlinear and hysteresis system using LABView and MATLAB o Integration of control algorithms on dsPIC controller for real time implementation

Csir Ceeri as Sr. Project Assistance

Feb 2018 to Mar 2020

Responsibilities are to assist in designing and development of Embedded Control System for providing excitation signal and measurement system

o Develop the Al based Closed loop and Feed Forward Control algorithms for highly nonlinear and hysteresis system using LABView and MATLAB

o Integration of control algorithms on dsPIC controller for real time implementation

ROBOKITS INDIA as Technical Support and Sales Leader Mar 2017 to Jan 2018

Team lead for technical support for accurate and necessary flow of technical information

- o Work for the increased sales through telephonic marketing
- o Assist in the developed product testing and prepare the technical datasheets and application notes
- o Communicate with the inventory and shipping department
- o Manage the products information on website from backend

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Instrumentation) from gujarat technological university in 2013

PG: M.Tech (Instrumentation) from GUJARAT TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY in 2016

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

GATE - (IN)

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Embedded C			
Python, MATLAB, LabVIEW			
Verilog (Novaice)			
MATLAB/Simulink,(DAQ), Keil, Mplab			
Arduino, micro controller		0	0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
dsPIC33F, ARM7/STM32			
Raspberry pi (Board - B2)			
MATLAB, OpenCV + Python			
Microsoft Office, Excel, PowerPoint			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
Japanese				
English				
Hindi				
Gujarati				
Rajasthani				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time